System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, 1976-2018
  - Stuttgart, Germany, 1989
    - Proceedings, 1989
      - DiStefano, Julia M., "A Metalanguage Communication, Confidence and CommitmentA New Perspective on Influence Diagrams", 1989
      - Drew, Donald R. with Antonio A. Trani and Lev A. Malakhoff, "System Dynamics Modeling of Air Warfare", 1989
      - Dyner, Isaac with Luz Mery Berrio and Adriana Bolivar, "Elements for Periurban Dynamics", 1989
      - Feldberg, Rasmus with Carsten Knudsen, Morten Hindsholm and Erik Mosekildev, "Non-Linear Dynamic Phenomena in Electron Transfer Devices", 1989
      - Forrester, Jay W., "The System Dynamics National Model: Macrobehavior from Microstructure", 1989
      - Foschiani, Stefan, "Development and Use of System Dynamics Models as Tools for Strategic Planning of Flexible Assembly Systems", 1989
      - Goumas, Th. with Ar. Papasavvas and D. V. Papaconstantinou, "Energy Supply Modelling: The Case of the Cyclades", 1989
      - Graham, Alan K. with Peter M. Senge and John D. Sterman, "Computer-based Case Studies in Management Education and Research", 1989
      - Gupta, Govind, "A System Dynamics Model for Automation", 1989
      - Hald, B.G. with C.N. Laugesen, C. Nielsen, E. Mosekilde, E. R. Larsen and J. Engelbrecht, "Rössler Bands in Economic and Biological Systems", 1989
      - Hall, Roger I., "A Training Game and Behavioral Decision Making Research Tool: An Alternative Use of System Dynamics Simulation", 1989
      - Hommel, M.B. with C. McGowan, "Creating System Dynamics Models Hierarchically Using SADT", 1989
      - Jacobsen, Chanoch with Yitzhak Samuel, "Planned Organizational Change: Theory, Model, Data and Simulation", 1989
      - Kameyama, Saburo with Takahiro Kojima, Akira Uchino and Kinya Machida, "Accounting Measurement and Methodological Characteristics of Accounting Dynamics", 1989
      - Kim, Daniel H., "Learning Laboratories: Designing a Reflective Learning Environment", 1989
      - Klaue, Thomas with Michael Veitinger, "Flexible Manufacturing and it's Benefits for the Financial Situation of an Enterprise -A System-Dynamics- Assessment on Investment Calculation-", 1989
      - Klieinhans, Andreas M., "Knowledge-Based Modelling", 1989
      - Kluwe, R. H. with C. Musiak and H. Haider, "Modelling the Process of Complex System Control", 1989
      - LaRoche, U., "Modelling Business Strategies for Verification of Planning", 1989
      - Lehmann, Frank with Thomas Lehner and Jürgen Beckmann, "A System-Dynamics Examination of the Effects of the Mahaweli-Project in Sri Lanka", 1989
      - Li, Zhou-wei with Zhou Yong, "A S.D. Model for Rational Exploitation and Utilization of Water Resources in Arid and Semi-arid Areas", 1989
      - Lyneis, James M. with Maurice Gluckman, "Marketing Analysis and Forecasting as a Strategic Business Tool", 1989
      - Macedo, Julio, "Designing a Manufacturing Policy Using the Reference Approach and Alternative System Dynamics Support Methods", 1989
      - Mashayekhi, Ali N., "Water Resources Development Planning", 1989
      - Meadows, Dennis, "Gaming to Implement System Dynamics Models", 1989
      - Merten, Peter P., "Loop-Based Strategic Decision Support Systems- Theory and Application", 1989
      - Morecroft, John D. W. with David C. Lane and Paul S.Viita, "Modelling a Biotechnology Startup Firm", 1989
      - Műller-Merbach, Heiner, "The Structured Systems Approach for the for the Design of Optimisation and Simulation Models", 1989
      - Naill, Roger F. with Sharon D. Belanger, "A System Dynamics Model for National Energy Policy Planning", 1989
      - Pei, Weiman, "Fuzzy Evaluation on the Validity of System Dynamics Models", 1989
      - Rahn, R. Joel, "Aggregate Dynamics of a Population of Commodity Cycle Models", 1989
      - Rego, J. V., "Schedule Delays and New Financing for the Argentine Electricity Sector Growth", 1989
      - Richards, Edward T., "The Origins of Mass Warfare: A System Dynamics Approach", 1989
      - Richardson, George P. with Peter M. Senge, "Corporate and Statewide Perspectives on the Liability Insurance Crisis", 1989
      - Richardson, George P. with Jac A.M. Vennix, David M. Anderson, John Rohrbaugh and W.A. Wallace, "Eliciting Group Knowledge for Model-Building", 1989
      - Roche, Maurice, "System Dynamics Applications in the Sector of Electricity", 1989
      - Ryzhenkov, A.V., "A Critique of Roemer's Conception of Exploitation", 1989
      - Saeed, Khalid, "A DYNEX-Based Learning Laboratory for Economic Development Planning", 1989
      - Saeed, Khalid, "Government's Ability to Manage Political Conflict over the Course of Economic Development", 1989
      - Sancar, F. H. with S. Allenstein, "System Dynamics Simulation of Spatial Character,", 1989
      - Schmidt, Dieter, "Computerbased Decision Support of the Strategic Planning and Strategic Management with System Dynamic Models Illustrated by the Example of the German Federal Railway", 1989
      - Senge, Peter M., "Organizational Learning: A New Challenge of System Dynamics", 1989
      - Sterman, John D., "Misperceptions of Feedback in Dynamic Decision Making", 1989
      - Vázquez, Margarita with Manuel Liz, "System Formalitation and Models Building", 1989
      - Wang, Qifan with Bingyi Yang, "A Study on the Coordinated Development of the R&D and Socio-Economy for a Typical Large City in China Using System Dynamics Approach", 1989
      - Wang, Qifan with Wang Ying, "A System Dynamics Approach to the Function of the Economic Leverages in China's Economy", 1989
      - Wang, Qifan with Hongshan Yang and Manling Yang, "A Socio-Economy Development Strategy Study of a Typical Underdeveloped Coastal Open City", 1989
      - Wang, Qifan with Tingchun Huang, Huimin Fu and Jinqua Qui, "A Study of Shanghai's Industrial Structure", 1989
      - Wang, Qifan with Zhiping Yao and Guangle Yan, "Chaos Study in System Dynamics", 1989
      - Weidlich, Wolfgang, "Synergetics and Social Science", 1989
      - Weil, Henry Birdseye with Kenneth P. Veit, "Corporate Strategic Thinking: The Role of System Dynamics", 1989
      - Winch, Graham W., "Tomorrow, Today: System Dynamics Models or Expert Systems?", 1989
      - Wolstenholme, Eric F. with Sattar A. Al-Alusi, "Improving Insight and Understanding by Optimising System Dynamics", 1989
      - Xu, Quingri with Keyie Jin, "The Coordinative Development Between R&D and Tech-Acquisition in China", 1989
      - Xu, Qingri with Hanping Li, "Dynamic Modelling and Policy Analysis on Technological Progress and the Change of Industrial Structure", 1989
      - Xu, Jie with Wan Xuemei and Yan Guangle, "Quantitative Analysis of Inflation Issue in China", 1989
      - Xu, Qingrui with Zhu Keqin and Li Junjei, "A System Dynamic Model and Policy Analysis for National Education and Economy Development", 1989
      - Yang, Ching T. with Ansheng Cao, "A Study of Sensitive Test", 1989
      - Yang, Manlin, "The Dynamic Relationship Between Transportation and Other Industries in China", 1989
      - Zhao, Wen-Huang with Wang Hong-Bin and Gu Lin-Ming, "An Application of System Dynamics to the Research on the Strategy of Rural Development in Heilongjiang Province", 1989
  - La Jolla, CA, USA, 1988
    - Conference Website, 1988
    - Abstracts, 1988
    - Proceedings, 1988
      - Alwani, Mazen M. with Eric F. Wolstenholme and A.A. Al-Hudaib, "The Design and the Testing of Plans at Government Level in Kuwait", 1988
      - Beckmann, Jürgen with Nicolai V. Engelhardt, "System Dynamics as a Support for Cash Management Expert Systems", 1988
      - Cavana, Robert Y. with Eric Haywood, "A System Dynamics Model of the New Zealand Economy", 1988
      - Dangerfield, Brian C. with Carole A. Roberts, "A Model for Exploring Scenarios Surrounding the Spread of AIDS in the U.K.", 1988
      - Diehl, Ernst W., "Participatory Simulations as Training Tools – A Study Based on the Market Growth Model", 1988
      - Finkenwirth, Andre with Georg Doll, "System Dynamics Simulations for the Management of a Commercial Bank", 1988
      - Ford, Andrew, "System Dynamics and Uncertainty: Results of Two Applications of Formalized Sensitivity Analyses with System Dynamics Models of the Electric Utility Industry", 1988
      - Fritz, Richard G., "The Effect of Linguistic Structure on the Analytic Paradigm of System Dynamics", 1988
      - Fritz, Richard G., "Evaluating the Impact of Financial Repression on the Economic Development Pattern of the Philippines", 1988
      - Fugleberg, Ole with David F. Andersen, "Sensitivity of Econometric Estimates of System Parameters to Changes in Sampling Intervals, Measurement Error, and Process Error", 1988
      - Graham, Alan K., "Generic Models as a Basis for Computer-Based Case Studies", 1988
      - Homer, Jack B. with Peiwei Mi, "SDNET: An Integrated Communications Network and Database for the International System Dynamics Community", 1988
      - Homer, Jack B. with Ivan Somers, "Defense Program Lifecycle Management: A Dynamic Model for Policy Analysis", 1988
      - Jessen, Svein A., "Can Project Dynamics be Modelled?", 1988
      - Karsky, Michael, "The World Oil Market: A System Dynamics Approach", 1988
      - Keloharju, Raimo J.J., "Multi-Criteria Optimization in System Dynamics", 1988
      - Kivijärvi, Hannu with Markku Touminen, "Financial and Production Planning in a Manufacturing Firm: Dynamic and Multi-Attribute Strategic Analysis", 1988
      - Klaue, Thomas, "Capital Investment Planning for New Technologies- A System Dynamics Assessment on Economic Efficiency", 1988
      - Kumar, Rakesh, "Corporate Simulation Modelling for Strategic Planning: A Modular Approach Based on System Dynamics Method", 1988
      - Lei, Mingkai with Xiaoyong Zhang, "A Model of System Dynamics on Factory Management", 1988
      - Levine, Ralph L. with Jane L. Pearson and Nicholas Ialongo, "Modeling the Dynamics of a Family in Crisis", 1988
      - Milling, Peter M., "Subjective Knowledge Bases in Corporate Policy Making", 1988
      - Morecroft, John D.W., "Strategic Microworlds and System Dynamics Modelling", 1988
      - Radzicki, Michael J. with Michael G. Bowen, Robert G. Kuller and Hector H. Guerrero, "The Dynamics of Escalation Phenomenon", 1988
      - Saeed, Khalid, "System Dynamics Modelling for the Design of Change", 1988
      - Shiizuka, Hisao with Fumie Kouchi, Tomoko Toishi and Etsuko Toyoda, "System Behaviors on Educational Problems", 1988
      - Sterman, John D., "Modeling Managerial Behavior: Misperceptions of Feedback in a Dynamic Decisionmaking Experiment", 1988
      - Sturis, Jeppe with Eric Mosekilde, "Bifurcation Sequence in a Simple Model of Migratory Dynamics", 1988
      - Swart, Johan, "Behavioural Sensitivity of the Lotka-Volterra Model", 1988
      - Toro, M. with F. Gaona and Javier Aracil, "Oscillations and Chaos in Ecological Populations", 1988
      - Uhran, John J. Jr. with Nassir Ghiaseddin and Ramzi K. Bualuan, "Expert System Dynamics Modeling with GURU", 1988
      - Vennix, Jac A. M. with Jan W. Gubbels, Doeke Post and Henk J. Poppen, "A Structured Approach to Knowledge Acquisition In Model Development", 1988
      - Vermeulen, P.J. with W.J. Rossouw and M.J. Joubert, "A Decision Support Model for University Management", 1988
      - Wallace, Stuart D. with Fahriye H. Sancar, "An Integrative Approach to Water Resource Management: An Application in Madison, Wisconsin", 1988
      - White, Norman F., "The Relationship Between Health Care Interventions and Morbidity: Some Counter-Intuitive Implications of a Socio-Ecological Model", 1988
      - Wolstenholme, Eric F., "The Effectiveness of Management Information Systems", 1988
      - Xia, Yun Guan with Wan Kang Chen, "Description of Microeconomics by System Dynamics", 1988
      - Yang, Ching T. with Ansheng Cao, "Using System Dynamics Method to Analyse an Enterprise", 1988
      - Yang, Shi Shen, "Inventory Control and Forecasting", 1988
      - Young, Showing H. with Iwan B. Santoso, "A System Dynamics Approach to the Car Ownership Trend in Taiwan Urban Areas", 1988
      - Zhang, Xing, "The Application of System Dynamics in Solving a Dynamic Input-Output Model with Delays", 1988
  - Shanghai, China, 1987
    - Conference Website, 1987
    - Abstracts, 1987
    - Proceedings, 1987
      - Adler, Karen J., "Depression, Perception and Cognition", 1987
      - Bakken, Bent E., "A System Dynamics Approach to Group Formation and Productivity", 1987
      - Bakken, Bent E., "Simulation Games - Do People Really Learn?", 1987
      - Bapna, Raj Kumar with Sushil K. Sharma, "A Quantitative Performance Measure and Its Application to System Dynamics", 1987
      - Bapna, Raj Kumar with Sujoy Ghose and Sushil K. Sharma, "Beyond DYNAMO: Future System Dynamics Simulation Programming", 1987
      - Barlas, Yaman with Stanley Carpenter, "A Fundamental Philosophy of Science Question and Validation of System Dynamic Models", 1987
      - Breiter, Andres E., "Must Government Owned Enterprises Be Less Efficient Than Private Ones?", 1987
      - Clark, Thomas D., "Parks and Natural Resources Management: A Systems Study", 1987
      - Davidson, Pål I. with John D. Sterman and George Richardson, "A Petroleum Life Style Cycle Model for the United States with Endogenous Technology, Exploration, Recovery, and Demand", 1987
      - Diallo, Amadou with R. Joel Rahn, "Application of Modal Analysis to Large System Dynamics Models", 1987
      - Doll,Georg, "Sales-Oriented Product-Innovation-Rates A New System Dynamics Approach to Research & Development Budgeting", 1987
      - Drew, Donald R. with Lee D. Han, "System Dynamics Model of Infrastructure Induced Development of Taiwan", 1987
      - Eberlein, Robert L. with James H. Hines, "Model Restructuring", 1987
      - Fang, Meiqi, "A Dynamic Modelling System with Chinese Character DYNAMO as the Kernel --Software Tool for System Dynamics", 1987
      - Ford, Andrew with Peter Gardiner, "Bringing the Results of the Bonneville Project to the Classroom", 1987
      - Guetzkow, Harold, "Development and Utilization of Global/World Models in International Affairs", 1987
      - Horiuchi, Toshiyuki with Wang Mohang, Akira Shimizu and Toshiro Simada, "Design and Analysis of the Development Model in Chiba Prefecture", 1987
      - Hu,Yukui with Suling Jia, "System Dynamics Model for Studying the Impact of Tech-Progress on Economics", 1987
      - Jiang,Yongning, "Thought Criteria for Use of System Dynamics", 1987
      - Jin, Hui with Bao Lui and Jisong Kou, "Research of Decision and Planning on the Development of Tianjin Can Industry-Application of System Dynamics", 1987
      - Jutila, Sakari T., "Dynamic Modeling of Adoption, Rejection and Life Cycles of Innovations", 1987
      - Kameyama, Saburo Kameyama with Takahiro Kojima, Akira Uchino and Kinnya Machida, "Accounting Dynamics – Its Concepts and Model", 1987
      - Keloharju,Raimo, "Simplification by Planning: The Third Way", 1987
      - Kishi, Mitsuo with Keitaro Noda, Yuji Yamashita and Katashi Taguchi, "A Prototype Expert System for System Dynamics Modelling", 1987
      - Lambert, André with Louis Lohle-Tart, "A Systemic View of the Population of China, Today and Tomorrow", 1987
      - Lee, Jiyang and Qifan Wang, "Applying System Dynamics to the Study of Pharmacokinetics and Pharmacodynamics", 1987
      - Li, Puhua with Chunpeng Tang, "SD Model of Urban Water Using of Tianjin", 1987
      - Lin,Ruiji, "CISD- - A Normative Method for Technology Assessment", 1987
      - Millen, Roger Neil, "Process/Production Control: A System Dynamics Study", 1987
      - Milling, Peter M., "Manufacturing's Role in Innovation Diffusion and Technological Substitution", 1987
      - Moffatt, I., "Towards an Integrated, Intelligent Knowledge Based System for Dynamic Modelling", 1987
      - Paul ,H., "A System Dynamics Model of Transportation Energy Demand", 1987
      - Qin, Datang with Tongrun Zhao and Zhishan Wu, "An Application of System Dynamics to Beijing Urban Ecosystem Research", 1987
      - Rahn, R. Joel, "Aggregation of Oscillating Subsystems", 1987
      - Rego, Juan with Juan A. Vega, "Probabilistic Generation of Scenarios for Argentina, Using a Elemental Harrod-Domar Model of Growth", 1987
      - Roberts, Nancy with Tim Barclay and Tim Kreutzer, "Modeling Tools for Problem-Solving", 1987
      - Sancar, Fahriye Hazer, "Implementation and Evaluation of a Modeling Approach to Community Development Planning Meeting the Challenge of Paradigm Breakdown", 1987
      - Schoenberg, Ronald with Albert J. Bergersen, "Decomposing the Long Wave Through a Non-Parametric Stochastic Measurement Model", 1987
      - Senge, Peter, "Catalyzing Systems Thinking within Organizations", 1987
      - Shimada, Toshiro Shimada with Kenji Fukushima, Hirokazu Mizushima, Kinya Machida and Akira Uchino, "A Simulation Model for Dental Diseases", 1987
      - Shorb, Alan McK, "Money- A Systems View", 1987
      - Sun, Dongchuan Sun, "R-SD: The Comprehensive Development and Utilization of Water Resources of Rivers", 1987
      - Tao, Jianhua with Ming Tang, Xing Zhang and Jinfang Chen, "The Mechanism and Program of Demand and Supply of Talent in ESE (Education-Society-Economy) System", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan, "Philosophical Views and Basic Theories of System Dynamics", 1987
      - Wang, Qifan with Bingyi Wang, "The Comparative Study of System Dynamics and Synergetics", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Jianglin Dong, "A Look into the Future of Microelectronics in China", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Guangle Yan, "The Parameter Quasi-Optimization for System Dynamic Models", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Haizhou Huang, "The Comparative Study on System Dynamics and Grey System Theory", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Haizhou Huang, "The System Dynamics Analysis of the National Financial and Monetary System of China", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Ma Shan, "Some of the Limits to the Growth of Big City in China", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Bing Wu and Jianglin Dong, "Economic Structure Changes and Their Impacts on Chinese Economy", 1987
      - Wang,Qifan with Xinnong Yang, "The Coordinative Development of Boomtown in Industry, Society in China", 1987
      - Wang, Xiaoting with Qifan Wang, "The Behavior of Industrial and Investment Structures in the Change of Demand and Supply", 1987
      - Wang, Hongbin with Demin Yao, "The System Dynamics Model for Policy Analysis of the Forest Industry System", 1987
      - Wu, Jianzhong with Gang Wu, "Rural Dynamics: A Study on the Exploitation and Protection of the Rural Resources in a Southern Province of China", 1987
      - Wu, Wenhua with Chingrui Xu and Shaozhong Jiang, "General System Dynamics Simulation Software System – ZU-DYNAMO", 1987
      - Xia, Yunguan Xia with Wangkang Chen, "The Study of Planned Economy and Market Economy of Oil and Engine Demand in the Equilibrium System through S.D.", 1987
      - Xu, Chingrui Xu with Shaozhong Jiang, Yiqun Xing and Jiasheng Wang, "Dynamic Modeling and Policy Analysis for National R&D Resource Allocation Decisions", 1987
      - Yang, Ching T. with Zi-yuan Xu, "A Tentative SD Model Applicable to the Study of Local Education Development Strategy and Policy Analysis in the Urban Area of Shanghai", 1987
      - Zhang, Jue, "Control and Administration of the Investment Hanger and Consuming Expansion", 1987
      - Zhang, Nai-guang with Cheng-hong Hu, "A System Dynamics Model and Policy Analysis for Rural Socio-Economic Development of a Provincial Lake Area", 1987
      - Zhu, Mingjie with Chenghong Hu, "Application of System Dynamics to Cardiovascular System Biofeedback Regulation of BP for Hypertensives", 1987
  - Seville, Spain, 1986
    - Conference Website, 1986
    - Abstracts, 1986
    - Proceedings, 1986
      - Alonso, Juan C. with Javier A. Alonso and Manuel Quintanilla, "Modeling the Common Crane (Grus grus) Population Wintering in Iberia", 1986
      - Andersen, David F. with Catherine Crawford, Sue R. Faerman and Erik Mosekilde, "A Simulation Model of Occupational Injury and Illness Causation and Regulation", 1986
      - Andretta, M. with M. Lugaresi, P. Mazzanti and R. Serra, "MAPS: an Expert Advisor for the Qualitative Analysis of Dynamical Systems", 1986
      - Antunes, Paula with António Camara, "A New Approach to Environmental Impact Assessment", 1986
      - Arif, M. Tasrif with Khalid Saeed, "Economic Growth and Development Policy in Oil Dependent Indonesia", 1986
      - Balbi, J.H with N. Balbi, G. Girolami, P. Orenga and G. Simonnot, "Identification of Dynamic Systems", 1986
      - Barton, Patrick with Mike Bull, "Planning Conservation Programs Decision Support with the Conservation Policy Analysis Model", 1986
      - Beijdorff, R. O., "CRISYS: A Model of the Criminal Justice System in the Netherlands", 1986
      - Beijdorff, R.O., "Development of a Policy-Supporting Simulation Model of the Records Management System of the Dutch Public Authorities", 1986
      - Breiter, Andres Esteban, "Is Systems Dynamics Rate of Diffusion Slow?", 1986
      - Bueno, Jose María with José A. D. Machuca, "The Role of the Women in Business Management", 1986
      - Büttner, Peter, "Molecule and Generic Structure for Synergy", 1986
      - Cabrer Borras, Bernardino with Amparo Sancho Perez, "Prospective Study of the Footwear Sector.", 1986
      - Câmara, A. with P. Antunes, M. Pinheiro and J. Seixas, "Linguistic Dynamic Modelling Using Logic Programming", 1986
      - Chong-Hui, Fan with Zhang Yi-Min, "The Time Delay and Oscillation of Economic System", 1986
      - Diehl, Ernst W., "A Multi-Sector Model of Inventory-Production Fluctuations: The Impact of Local Information on Global Performance", 1986
      - Eberlein, Robert L., "Full Feedback Parameter Estimation", 1986
      - Eberlein, Robert L., "Identifying and Displaying Important Feedback Paths", 1986
      - Eijdems, H.H.E.W. with D.J. Sweeny, B.J. Brouwer, W.R. Snel and J .M. den Breeje, "Industrial Site Planning as a Tool to Control Regional Employment -A DYNAMO Model -", 1986
      - Fontela, Emilio with Antonio Pulido and Ana del Sur, "The Causal Structure of the Wharton-UAM Model of the Spanish Economy", 1986
      - Forrester, Jay W., "Lessons from System Dynamics Modeling", 1986
      - Gaci, M. with A. Babaamer LSC: A Portable Continuous Simulation Software", 1986
      - Garcia, Moisés Garcia with Francisco Serrano Moracho, "System Dynamics and Circulatory Analysis: Proposals for an Alliance", 1986
      - Gil, I. with M.I. Aguinagalde, M. Graña, J. Dolado and F.J. Torrealdea, "Dynamical Interaction between Languages: Castilian and Basque a System Dynamics Model", 1986
      - Gómez-Cia, T. with Laura Roa Romero and Lazo Zbykowski, "Dynamic Analysis of the Influence of Reanimation Treatment in Burned Patients", 1986
      - González Cristobal, Jose Carlos with Gregorio Fernández, "EASDM: An Expert Aid for System Dynamics Modelling", 1986
      - Hall, Roger I. A System-Behavioral Methodology for Business Policy Research", 1986
      - Herremans, Albert with Philippe Wilmes, "Evaluation of the Benefits from Using System Dynamics on Personal Computers for Corporate Financial Management", 1986
      - Homer, Jack with Richard John and William Cotreau, "A Dynamic Model for Understanding Eating Disorders", 1986
      - Keloharju, R. with E. F. Wolstenholme A Case Study in System Dynamics Optimisation", 1986
      - Kleinhans, Andreas, "A Behavior Analysis Expert System for System Dynamics Models", 1986
      - Kivijärvi, Hannu with Margareta Soismaa, "An Investment and Pricing Problem: A System Dynamics Approach to the Differential Games", 1986
      - Krallmann, H. with B. Rieger, "Development of a Common Communication and Control System for System Dynamics Type of Simulation Models", 1986